{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689625085","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689625085"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 8e07ecc6-c331-4c7a-aee3-bea5675a816b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689629906","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689629905"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 8e07ecc6-c331-4c7a-aee3-bea5675a816b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689634103","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689634103"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 8e07ecc6-c331-4c7a-aee3-bea5675a816b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689641017","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689641016"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 8e07ecc6-c331-4c7a-aee3-bea5675a816b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689641869","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689641869"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 8e07ecc6-c331-4c7a-aee3-bea5675a816b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689660091","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689660091"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 6d5d54d0-fe11-451b-acf7-2e8a8d34c9ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_7-6-0"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689669283","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689669283"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 6d5d54d0-fe11-451b-acf7-2e8a8d34c9ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_0-1-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689674644","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689674644"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 6d5d54d0-fe11-451b-acf7-2e8a8d34c9ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_4-2-0"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689680346","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689680346"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 6d5d54d0-fe11-451b-acf7-2e8a8d34c9ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_0-6-3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689685922","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689685922"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 6d5d54d0-fe11-451b-acf7-2e8a8d34c9ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-8-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689691779","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689691779"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 6d5d54d0-fe11-451b-acf7-2e8a8d34c9ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_5-3-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689698765","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689698765"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 6d5d54d0-fe11-451b-acf7-2e8a8d34c9ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_8-6-7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689706752","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689706751"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 6d5d54d0-fe11-451b-acf7-2e8a8d34c9ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_1-7-4"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689713002","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689713002"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 6d5d54d0-fe11-451b-acf7-2e8a8d34c9ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_6-8-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689718628","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689718628"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 6d5d54d0-fe11-451b-acf7-2e8a8d34c9ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-6-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689725193","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689725192"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 6d5d54d0-fe11-451b-acf7-2e8a8d34c9ba"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.mc.11"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-6-1"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689751408","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689751408"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689755649","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689755649"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689759524","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689759524"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689763802","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689763802"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689770727","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689770727"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689775859","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689775859"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689779442","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689779442"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689783461","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689783461"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689788541","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689788541"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689792613","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689792613"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689797291","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689797290"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689800909","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689800908"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689804305","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689804305"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689807914","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689807914"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689811582","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689811582"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689815447","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689815447"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689819852","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689819852"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689823705","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689823705"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689827335","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689827335"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689831032","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689831032"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689836307","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689836307"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689840326","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689840326"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689843560","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689843559"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689846655","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689846655"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689852441","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689852438"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 69f31b8d-15f3-4728-9ed6-43932bb937f9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689882091","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689882091"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 7664b92e-4b16-4462-b91b-2702a82a2318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689884981","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689884981"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 7664b92e-4b16-4462-b91b-2702a82a2318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689904068","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689904068"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 7664b92e-4b16-4462-b91b-2702a82a2318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689923642","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689923641"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 7664b92e-4b16-4462-b91b-2702a82a2318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689944297","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689944296"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 7664b92e-4b16-4462-b91b-2702a82a2318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689965642","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689965642"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 7664b92e-4b16-4462-b91b-2702a82a2318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689980841","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689980840"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 7664b92e-4b16-4462-b91b-2702a82a2318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" page_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543689980954","data":{"timestamp":" 1543689980954"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 7664b92e-4b16-4462-b91b-2702a82a2318"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690009793","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690009792"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" de9904ff-fe84-4fa6-8ecd-8cef1ee49af5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690028887","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690028887"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" de9904ff-fe84-4fa6-8ecd-8cef1ee49af5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690170753","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690170752"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" de9904ff-fe84-4fa6-8ecd-8cef1ee49af5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690170831","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690170831"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" de9904ff-fe84-4fa6-8ecd-8cef1ee49af5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIPYA"," userResponse":" JIPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690179136","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690179136"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" de9904ff-fe84-4fa6-8ecd-8cef1ee49af5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690194993","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690194992"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" KUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690202773","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690202772"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690205124","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690205123"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690208344","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690208344"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690210714","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690210713"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nane"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690213457","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690213457"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nane"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690215848","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690215847"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690217728","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690217727"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" saba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690220219","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690220218"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690221807","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690221807"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sita"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690224161","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690224161"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690227654","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690227654"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tano"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690229944","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690229944"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690231145","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690231145"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nne"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690233528","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690233527"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690234866","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690234865"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690237404","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690237404"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" MBILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690243598","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690243598"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" START_MBILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690247256","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690247255"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbili"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBILI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690249632","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690249632"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690253412","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690253412"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moja"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690256068","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690256067"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFURI"," userResponse":" SIFURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690260616","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690260616"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFURI"," userResponse":" SIFURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690262629","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690262628"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690262737","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690262737"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIFURI"," userResponse":" SIFURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690281226","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690281226"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" b3946e7f-118a-4e2c-9d14-d3c22d6b5e7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__0..10.SS_OFF1_DES.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" sifuri"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690325632","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690325632"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 4a3660a0-0d28-4980-90df-32677269e8fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kimya_tamu-kimya-kuliko-chako"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kimya"," userResponse":" kimya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690347895","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690347892"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 4a3660a0-0d28-4980-90df-32677269e8fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" kimya_tamu-kimya-kuliko-chako"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690348022","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690348022"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 4a3660a0-0d28-4980-90df-32677269e8fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hadi anapohisi njaa ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690359338","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690359337"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690359724","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690359724"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690360216","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690360215"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690360567","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690360567"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690360979","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690360979"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690361459","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690361459"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690361692","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690361692"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690364946","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690364946"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690364990","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690364990"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690365719","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690365718"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690366122","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690366122"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690366426","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690366426"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690366638","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690366638"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690366836","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690366836"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690367162","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690367161"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690367394","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690367394"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690370626","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690370625"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690371034","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690371034"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690373654","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690373654"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690373861","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690373861"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690374068","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690374068"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690377595","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690377594"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690381372","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690381371"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690382404","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690382404"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690385090","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690385090"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690385472","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690385471"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690385963","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690385962"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690386319","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690386317"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690386732","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690386732"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690387219","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690387219"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690387450","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690387450"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690390654","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690390653"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690390696","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690390696"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690391426","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690391425"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690391830","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690391829"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690392131","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690392130"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690392342","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690392342"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690392543","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690392543"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690392864","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690392864"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690393100","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690393099"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690395779","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690395778"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690395851","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690395851"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2q.AV.rise.12__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690407150","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690407150"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" eeebefd3-1705-4246-b83f-dae1dc8362ab"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690429184","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690429184"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 96472243-be7b-437e-8697-c3b7a6b36650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_ch_n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690435814","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690435814"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 96472243-be7b-437e-8697-c3b7a6b36650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_o_ch_r"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690442435","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690442435"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 96472243-be7b-437e-8697-c3b7a6b36650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_z_t_ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690449098","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690449097"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 96472243-be7b-437e-8697-c3b7a6b36650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_d_ch_k"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690455741","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690455741"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 96472243-be7b-437e-8697-c3b7a6b36650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_n_ch_w"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690462367","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690462367"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 96472243-be7b-437e-8697-c3b7a6b36650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_y_j_ch"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690469029","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690469029"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 96472243-be7b-437e-8697-c3b7a6b36650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_o_i"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690475679","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690475679"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 96472243-be7b-437e-8697-c3b7a6b36650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_g_k"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690482342","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690482342"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 96472243-be7b-437e-8697-c3b7a6b36650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_p_ch_v"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690488997","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690488997"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 96472243-be7b-437e-8697-c3b7a6b36650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ch_z_o"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690502150","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690502150"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 96472243-be7b-437e-8697-c3b7a6b36650"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_ch_z_o"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690539107","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690539107"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 379af664-7ae0-4bfe-88e3-1634f86caa0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" njaa_baba-njaa-ambayo-hadithi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" njaa"," userResponse":" njaa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690570148","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690570148"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 379af664-7ae0-4bfe-88e3-1634f86caa0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yake_tena-kuwa-kisha-yake"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" yake"," userResponse":" kisha"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690574801","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690574801"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 379af664-7ae0-4bfe-88e3-1634f86caa0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yake_tena-kuwa-kisha-yake"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" yake"," userResponse":" yake"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690611196","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690611196"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 379af664-7ae0-4bfe-88e3-1634f86caa0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kichekesho_duni-kichekesho-ukatili-pumua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kichekesho"," userResponse":" kichekesho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690637813","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690637813"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 379af664-7ae0-4bfe-88e3-1634f86caa0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kimya_kuna-kimya-tofauti-ndiyo"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kimya"," userResponse":" kimya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690660483","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690660483"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 379af664-7ae0-4bfe-88e3-1634f86caa0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nini_katika-mamba-nini-moto"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nini"," userResponse":" nini"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690669458","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690669456"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 379af664-7ae0-4bfe-88e3-1634f86caa0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" nini_katika-mamba-nini-moto"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690669580","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690669580"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 379af664-7ae0-4bfe-88e3-1634f86caa0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690679023","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690679022"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 379af664-7ae0-4bfe-88e3-1634f86caa0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.5__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690690324","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690690323"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 379af664-7ae0-4bfe-88e3-1634f86caa0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690697534","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690697534"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 379af664-7ae0-4bfe-88e3-1634f86caa0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_9"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690769342","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690769342"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" ac3e0164-d749-46c8-82ce-b4f7f7c4f4ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tena_fisi-zake-tena-za"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" tena"," userResponse":" tena"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690788801","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690788799"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" ac3e0164-d749-46c8-82ce-b4f7f7c4f4ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" tena_fisi-zake-tena-za"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690788890","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690788890"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" ac3e0164-d749-46c8-82ce-b4f7f7c4f4ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690856431","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690856430"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 3ea044af-255d-49c7-9b12-5aabbfbe4b83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tena_zake-tena-za-fisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" tena"," userResponse":" tena"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690875688","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690875684"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 3ea044af-255d-49c7-9b12-5aabbfbe4b83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" tena_zake-tena-za-fisi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690875768","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690875768"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 3ea044af-255d-49c7-9b12-5aabbfbe4b83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690885311","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690885311"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 3ea044af-255d-49c7-9b12-5aabbfbe4b83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.reveal::1..4.SD_OFF1_INC.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690892607","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690892607"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 3ea044af-255d-49c7-9b12-5aabbfbe4b83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690900056","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690900055"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 3ea044af-255d-49c7-9b12-5aabbfbe4b83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_10"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hamisi alifurahi ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690912364","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690912364"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c534b2c7-1cc5-4607-a464-4a73dfd9ca43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DAU"," userResponse":" DAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690962101","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690962100"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c534b2c7-1cc5-4607-a464-4a73dfd9ca43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dau"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DAU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690963717","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690963716"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c534b2c7-1cc5-4607-a464-4a73dfd9ca43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dereva"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" DEREVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690967824","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690967824"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c534b2c7-1cc5-4607-a464-4a73dfd9ca43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dereva"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" DEREVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690969427","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690969427"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c534b2c7-1cc5-4607-a464-4a73dfd9ca43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOGO"," userResponse":" DOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690983196","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690983196"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c534b2c7-1cc5-4607-a464-4a73dfd9ca43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dogo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOGO"," userResponse":" DOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690984774","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690984774"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c534b2c7-1cc5-4607-a464-4a73dfd9ca43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dudu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUDU"," userResponse":" DUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690991332","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690991332"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c534b2c7-1cc5-4607-a464-4a73dfd9ca43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dudu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUDU"," userResponse":" DUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690992941","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690992940"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c534b2c7-1cc5-4607-a464-4a73dfd9ca43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" debe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEBE"," userResponse":" DEBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543690998924","data":{"timestamp":" 1543690998923"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c534b2c7-1cc5-4607-a464-4a73dfd9ca43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" debe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEBE"," userResponse":" DEBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691000541","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691000541"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c534b2c7-1cc5-4607-a464-4a73dfd9ca43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dobi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOBI"," userResponse":" DOBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691004187","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691004187"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c534b2c7-1cc5-4607-a464-4a73dfd9ca43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dobi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOBI"," userResponse":" DOBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691005837","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691005837"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c534b2c7-1cc5-4607-a464-4a73dfd9ca43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691012585","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691012584"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c534b2c7-1cc5-4607-a464-4a73dfd9ca43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691014199","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691014199"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c534b2c7-1cc5-4607-a464-4a73dfd9ca43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" duma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUMA"," userResponse":" DUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691019621","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691019621"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c534b2c7-1cc5-4607-a464-4a73dfd9ca43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" duma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUMA"," userResponse":" DUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691021644","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691021643"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c534b2c7-1cc5-4607-a464-4a73dfd9ca43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" duma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691021745","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691021745"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c534b2c7-1cc5-4607-a464-4a73dfd9ca43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.43"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" duma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUMA"," userResponse":" DUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691035296","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691035296"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691035930","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691035930"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691036731","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691036731"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691037897","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691037897"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANAISHI"," userResponse":" PANAISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691038348","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691038347"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691039131","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691039131"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Katika kijiji chetu panaishi Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691041502","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691041502"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691042337","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691042336"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691043179","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691043179"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691043829","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691043828"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691044059","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691044058"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691044793","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691044793"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADOA"," userResponse":" MADOA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691045643","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691045642"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUSI"," userResponse":" MEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691045841","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691045841"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691046680","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691046679"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUPE"," userResponse":" MEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691047288","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691047288"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691047829","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691047828"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691048662","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691048662"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio ana paka wa madoa meusi na meupe kwa jina Safi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691051456","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691051456"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691052199","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691052199"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691053253","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691053253"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPOENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691054210","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691054209"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZINI"," userResponse":" KAZINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691055423","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691055422"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAACHA"," userResponse":" ANAACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691056042","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691056041"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691056815","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691056815"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio anapoenda kazini anaacha mlango wazi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZI"," userResponse":" WAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691059976","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691059975"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691060928","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691060928"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKAA"," userResponse":" ANAKAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691062032","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691062032"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691062116","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691062116"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691062995","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691062993"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691063596","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691063596"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691064472","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691064471"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUILINDA"," userResponse":" KUILINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691065024","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691065024"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691065234","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691065234"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691065709","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691065708"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691066496","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691066495"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi anakaa katikati ya mlango na kuilinda nyumba ya Bwana Kiio."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691069555","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691069555"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691069743","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691069743"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691070552","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691070546"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691071992","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691071992"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIKARIBIA"," userResponse":" AKIKARIBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691072978","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691072978"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691074829","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691074829"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKODOLEA"," userResponse":" ANAMKODOLEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691075531","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691075531"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691076072","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691076072"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691077492","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691077491"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUNYOOSHEA"," userResponse":" KUMUNYOOSHEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691078231","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691078230"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHA"," userResponse":" KUCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691079031","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691079031"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa wa jirani akikaribia Safi anamkodolea macho na kumunyooshea kucha zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691081890","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691081890"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691083428","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691083427"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATOROKA"," userResponse":" ANATOROKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691083721","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691083719"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691084388","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691084388"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUDI"," userResponse":" KURUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691084835","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691084834"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbwa anatoroka na kurudi kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691088273","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691088273"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691089892","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691089891"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITOKEZEA"," userResponse":" AKITOKEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691091248","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691091248"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691091514","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691091514"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YU"," userResponse":" YU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691092523","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691092523"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691093992","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691093992"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani akitokezea Safi yu tayari kumkwaruza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMKWARUZA"," userResponse":" KUMKWARUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691097267","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691097267"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIRANI"," userResponse":" JIRANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691098435","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691098434"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAGEUKA"," userResponse":" ANAGEUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691099170","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691099170"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" MBIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691099773","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691099773"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691100327","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691100327"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691100860","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691100860"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jirani anageuka mbio na kwenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691104028","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691104028"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691104949","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691104948"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIHISI"," userResponse":" AKIHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691105697","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691105696"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691107015","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691107014"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFUNGA"," userResponse":" ANAFUNGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691107778","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691107777"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691108029","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691108029"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691109527","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691109527"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akihisi njaa anafunga mlango kwa kuusukuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUUSUKUMA"," userResponse":" KUUSUKUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691113128","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691113127"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAINGIA"," userResponse":" ANAINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691113765","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691113765"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691113993","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691113992"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691114590","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691114590"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691115373","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691115373"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691116123","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691116122"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaingia ndani na kula chakula chake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" CHAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691119394","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691119394"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691120984","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691120983"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIMALIZA"," userResponse":" AKIMALIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691122373","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691122373"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" ANARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691123100","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691123100"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691123357","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691123357"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691123960","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691123959"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOFA"," userResponse":" SOFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691124179","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691124178"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691125026","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691125025"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Safi akimaliza anaruka juu ya sofa na kulala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691128338","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691128337"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unachosikia ni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNACHOSIKIA"," userResponse":" UNACHOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691128722","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691128721"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unachosikia ni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691129670","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691129669"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unachosikia ni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PURR"," userResponse":" PURR"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691132737","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691132737"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691133709","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691133706"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691135229","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691135228"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWASILI"," userResponse":" AKIWASILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691136252","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691136251"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691137693","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691137692"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJINYOOSHA"," userResponse":" HUJINYOOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691139526","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691139526"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691140693","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691140692"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691140974","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691140974"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691142284","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691142284"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMKARIBISHA"," userResponse":" KUMKARIBISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691143342","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691143340"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio akiwasili Safi hujinyoosha kwa furaha na kumkaribisha nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691146295","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691146294"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691146959","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691146959"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIIO"," userResponse":" KIIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691147171","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691147170"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691147778","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691147776"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAFI"," userResponse":" SAFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691148950","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691148950"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAKETI"," userResponse":" WANAKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691149634","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691149634"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691149923","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691149923"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691150852","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691150851"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691151963","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691151962"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691152841","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691152840"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691154067","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691154067"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKISOMA"," userResponse":" AKISOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691155358","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691155357"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAZETI"," userResponse":" GAZETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_11","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691157874","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691157871"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691157986","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691157986"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GAZETI"," userResponse":" GAZETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691184992","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691184992"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691195479","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691195479"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.84","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691202845","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691202845"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" 001d3d92-8918-4daf-ab9d-a9b699180860"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_11"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Bwana Kiio na Safi wanaketi karibu na moto kila mmoja akisoma gazeti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691215188","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691215187"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jembe lake lilikuwa fupi mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEMBE"," userResponse":" JEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691215768","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691215768"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jembe lake lilikuwa fupi mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKE"," userResponse":" LAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691216662","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691216662"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jembe lake lilikuwa fupi mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691217356","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691217355"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jembe lake lilikuwa fupi mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691217818","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691217818"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jembe lake lilikuwa fupi mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691221160","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691221160"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlango wake ulikuwa chini mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691221642","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691221642"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlango wake ulikuwa chini mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691222666","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691222666"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlango wake ulikuwa chini mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIKUWA"," userResponse":" ULIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691223340","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691223340"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlango wake ulikuwa chini mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691223832","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691223832"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mlango wake ulikuwa chini mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691226994","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691226993"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kitanda chake kilikuwa kifupi mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" KITANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691227614","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691227614"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kitanda chake kilikuwa kifupi mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" CHAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691228408","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691228407"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kitanda chake kilikuwa kifupi mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILIKUWA"," userResponse":" KILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691229390","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691229390"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kitanda chake kilikuwa kifupi mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFUPI"," userResponse":" KIFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691229825","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691229825"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kitanda chake kilikuwa kifupi mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691233182","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691233182"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baisikeli yake ilikuwa fupi mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISIKELI"," userResponse":" BAISIKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691233775","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691233774"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baisikeli yake ilikuwa fupi mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691234637","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691234637"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baisikeli yake ilikuwa fupi mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691235375","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691235375"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baisikeli yake ilikuwa fupi mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691235806","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691235805"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baisikeli yake ilikuwa fupi mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691238589","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691238588"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu huyu alikuwa mrefu zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691239021","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691239021"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu huyu alikuwa mrefu zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691239791","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691239790"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu huyu alikuwa mrefu zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691240848","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691240848"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu huyu alikuwa mrefu zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691241838","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691241838"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu huyu alikuwa mrefu zaidi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691245663","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691245661"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitengeneza mpini wa jembe mrefu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITENGENEZA"," userResponse":" ALITENGENEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691246449","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691246448"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitengeneza mpini wa jembe mrefu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPINI"," userResponse":" MPINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691246694","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691246694"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitengeneza mpini wa jembe mrefu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691247280","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691247279"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitengeneza mpini wa jembe mrefu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEMBE"," userResponse":" JEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691248278","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691248277"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitengeneza mpini wa jembe mrefu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691249057","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691249057"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitengeneza mpini wa jembe mrefu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691252973","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691252972"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitengeneza fremu refu za mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITENGENEZA"," userResponse":" ALITENGENEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691253970","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691253969"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitengeneza fremu refu za mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FREMU"," userResponse":" FREMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691254561","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691254560"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitengeneza fremu refu za mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REFU"," userResponse":" REFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691255096","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691255095"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitengeneza fremu refu za mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691255890","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691255889"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitengeneza fremu refu za mlango."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLANGO"," userResponse":" MLANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691259724","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691259723"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitengeneza kitanda kirefu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITENGENEZA"," userResponse":" ALITENGENEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691260560","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691260559"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitengeneza kitanda kirefu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITANDA"," userResponse":" KITANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691261495","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691261495"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitengeneza kitanda kirefu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIREFU"," userResponse":" KIREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691262250","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691262249"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitengeneza kitanda kirefu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691265269","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691265269"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akanunua baiskikeli iliyo refu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691266543","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691266543"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akanunua baiskikeli iliyo refu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKANUNUA"," userResponse":" AKANUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691267494","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691267493"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akanunua baiskikeli iliyo refu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISKIKELI"," userResponse":" BAISKIKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691268368","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691268367"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akanunua baiskikeli iliyo refu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYO"," userResponse":" ILIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691268931","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691268931"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akanunua baiskikeli iliyo refu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REFU"," userResponse":" REFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691269737","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691269736"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akanunua baiskikeli iliyo refu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691273177","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691273176"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi juu ya kiti kilichokuwa juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKETI"," userResponse":" ALIKETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691273529","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691273528"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi juu ya kiti kilichokuwa juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691273752","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691273751"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi juu ya kiti kilichokuwa juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691274307","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691274306"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi juu ya kiti kilichokuwa juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITI"," userResponse":" KITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691275294","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691275294"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi juu ya kiti kilichokuwa juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOKUWA"," userResponse":" KILICHOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691275923","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691275923"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi juu ya kiti kilichokuwa juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691276553","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691276553"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliketi juu ya kiti kilichokuwa juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691279491","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691279490"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikula kwa kutumia uma iliyokuwa refu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKULA"," userResponse":" ALIKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691279766","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691279765"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikula kwa kutumia uma iliyokuwa refu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691280649","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691280649"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikula kwa kutumia uma iliyokuwa refu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" KUTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691281212","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691281212"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikula kwa kutumia uma iliyokuwa refu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMA"," userResponse":" UMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691282331","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691282331"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikula kwa kutumia uma iliyokuwa refu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691283060","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691283059"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikula kwa kutumia uma iliyokuwa refu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REFU"," userResponse":" REFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691283493","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691283493"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikula kwa kutumia uma iliyokuwa refu mno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691286967","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691286967"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliacha nyumba yake na kuishi katika msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIACHA"," userResponse":" ALIACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691287471","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691287471"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliacha nyumba yake na kuishi katika msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691288126","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691288124"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliacha nyumba yake na kuishi katika msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691288762","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691288762"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliacha nyumba yake na kuishi katika msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691289448","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691289448"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliacha nyumba yake na kuishi katika msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUISHI"," userResponse":" KUISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691290125","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691290125"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliacha nyumba yake na kuishi katika msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691291067","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691291067"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliacha nyumba yake na kuishi katika msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSITU"," userResponse":" MSITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691292042","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691292042"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliacha nyumba yake na kuishi katika msitu mkubwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691294838","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691294838"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi kwa miaka mingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691295097","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691295096"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi kwa miaka mingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691295840","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691295839"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi kwa miaka mingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691296899","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691296899"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi kwa miaka mingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGI"," userResponse":" MINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691299593","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691299591"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Aliishi kwa miaka mingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691299685","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691299685"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliishi kwa miaka mingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MINGI"," userResponse":" MINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.85","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691308415","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691308414"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliishi kwa miaka mingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691315269","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691315269"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliishi kwa miaka mingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.lc.7__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691322350","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691322350"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" bbb1857e-a59c-41d5-a27e-430aba6314f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_12"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Aliishi kwa miaka mingi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691334011","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691334011"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691334390","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691334390"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691335042","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691335042"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGI"," userResponse":" NYINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691335241","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691335240"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691336139","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691336138"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuna njia nyingi za kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691338494","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691338493"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nichague gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NICHAGUE"," userResponse":" NICHAGUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691339560","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691339559"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nichague gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691342320","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691342320"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691343422","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691343422"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691344147","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691344147"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie ndege?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691346876","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691346876"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691347849","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691347849"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INARUKA"," userResponse":" INARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691348543","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691348543"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691349296","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691349296"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndege inaruka juu sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691351476","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691351476"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691352238","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691352238"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOGOPA"," userResponse":" NAOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691352692","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691352692"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nami naogopa kuruka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691357514","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691357514"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691358297","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691358297"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691359423","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691359422"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nitumie helikopta?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691362425","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691362425"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691363295","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691363295"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691363519","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691363518"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691363890","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691363889"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691364037","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691364037"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691364671","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691364671"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini helikopta na ndege ni sawa!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691367591","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691367591"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691368514","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691368514"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691369432","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691369432"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691370086","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691370085"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691370170","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691370170"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691370732","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691370732"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au labda nitatumia gari la moshi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOSHI"," userResponse":" MOSHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691374052","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691374051"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691374926","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691374926"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" STESHENI"," userResponse":" STESHENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691375367","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691375366"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691376027","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691376027"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691376617","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691376615"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini stesheni iko mbali sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691379314","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691379314"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitachoka kutembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITACHOKA"," userResponse":" NITACHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691380168","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691380167"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitachoka kutembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691383089","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691383089"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691384282","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691384282"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691385060","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691385059"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie basi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691388262","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691388262"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJI"," userResponse":" KIJIJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691388702","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691388702"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHETU"," userResponse":" CHETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691389094","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691389094"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" KINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691389534","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691389532"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BASI"," userResponse":" BASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691389985","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691389985"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691390689","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691390689"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kijiji chetu kina basi moja pekee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691393992","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691393992"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691395082","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691395081"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691395469","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691395468"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691396432","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691396432"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda nitatumia lori kusafiri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691399701","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691399701"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691400540","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691400540"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691401517","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691401516"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASA"," userResponse":" HASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691402437","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691402437"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691402546","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691402546"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691403265","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691403265"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBEBEA"," userResponse":" KUBEBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691403952","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691403951"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZIGO"," userResponse":" MIZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691404685","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691404684"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini lori hasa ni la kubebea mizigo mizito."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIZITO"," userResponse":" MIZITO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691407467","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691407467"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691408832","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691408828"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITUMIE"," userResponse":" NITUMIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691409635","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691409635"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISKELI"," userResponse":" BAISKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691410854","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691410853"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je nitumie baiskeli kusafiri?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691413987","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691413987"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIJUI"," userResponse":" SIJUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691414527","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691414526"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691414846","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691414845"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691415800","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691415800"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATANIPATIA"," userResponse":" ATANIPATIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691416568","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691416568"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAISKELI"," userResponse":" BAISKELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691417174","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691417174"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sijui ikiwa baba atanipatia baiskeli yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691420055","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691420054"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AU"," userResponse":" AU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691420781","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691420780"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIJARIBU"," userResponse":" NIJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691421527","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691421527"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691421759","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691421755"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691422503","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691422502"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Au nijaribu kusafiri kwa mashua?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691425556","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691425556"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691425922","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691425921"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691426635","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691426634"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIAMINI"," userResponse":" SIAMINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691427228","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691427228"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASHUA"," userResponse":" MASHUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691427801","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691427801"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mimi siamini mashua sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691430695","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691430695"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AAH"," userResponse":" AAH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691433375","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691433375"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691434850","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691434850"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Najua nitakachotumia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKACHOTUMIA"," userResponse":" NITAKACHOTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691438230","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691438230"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITATUMIA"," userResponse":" NITATUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691438922","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691438922"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TREKTA"," userResponse":" TREKTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691440000","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691440000"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691442829","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691442828"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691442962","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691442961"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSAFIRI"," userResponse":" KUSAFIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691448253","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691448252"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2q.AV.rise.22","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691454056","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691454056"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_29","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691459204","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691459204"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" c93e6861-8cb7-43ea-a915-c72d2427de17"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_13"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nitatumia trekta kusafiri!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691469421","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691469420"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691469654","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691469654"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691470097","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691470097"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691470301","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691470301"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691471044","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691471044"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hii ni kamba ya kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691474087","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691474087"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691474947","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691474947"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANARUKA"," userResponse":" ANARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691475484","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691475484"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691476234","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691476234"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEKEE"," userResponse":" PEKEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691476573","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691476573"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaruka kamba pekee yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691479657","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691479657"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691480827","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691480827"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESHIKIWA"," userResponse":" AMESHIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691481295","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691481294"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMBA"," userResponse":" KAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691481531","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691481531"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691482282","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691482281"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691482700","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691482700"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi ameshikiwa kamba na rafiki yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691485695","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691485695"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691486328","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691486328"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691487145","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691487145"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASOMA"," userResponse":" ANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691487984","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691487978"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anasoma kitabu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITABU"," userResponse":" KITABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691490988","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691490988"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691492026","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691492026"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAAGA"," userResponse":" ANAWAAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691492634","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691492634"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691493195","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691493190"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anawaaga rafiki zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691496283","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691496282"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691497142","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691497142"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAOSHA"," userResponse":" ANAOSHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691497762","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691497762"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYOMBA"," userResponse":" VYOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691498600","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691498600"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaosha vyomba jikoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691501524","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691501524"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691502661","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691502661"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAANDIKA"," userResponse":" ANAANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691503757","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691503756"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anaandika ubaoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAONI"," userResponse":" UBAONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691507051","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691507050"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691507896","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691507895"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691508837","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691508837"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAKULA"," userResponse":" ANAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691509696","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691509695"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa Mumbi anakula matunda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691512996","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691512995"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691513310","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691513310"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691513872","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691513871"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691516543","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691516542"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691517551","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691517550"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi analala."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANALALA"," userResponse":" ANALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691520658","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691520658"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691522314","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691522314"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMZUNGUMZIA"," userResponse":" ANAMZUNGUMZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691523012","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691523012"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama anamzungumzia Mumbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691525968","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691525968"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUMBI"," userResponse":" MUMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691527236","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691527235"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ANAFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691530139","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691530134"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691530259","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691530259"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFIKIRIA"," userResponse":" ANAFIKIRIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691536786","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691536786"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::0..10.SD_OFF1_INC.7__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691541150","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691541150"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.show.86","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691546929","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691546929"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" e8c8ec5f-3680-40e7-be32-af66d08e7d73"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_14"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mumbi anafikiria."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691556307","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691556305"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691556803","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691556802"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691557963","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691557962"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAFAHAMU"," userResponse":" ANAFAHAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691558341","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691558340"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691558995","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691558994"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691559401","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691559401"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691560145","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691560144"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKONGA"," userResponse":" MKONGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691560926","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691560925"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila mtu anafahamu kuwa tembo ana mkonga mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691564113","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691564112"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691564614","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691564614"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691564901","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691564900"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691565369","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691565368"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691566086","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691566086"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691566800","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691566800"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691567611","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691567611"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691568308","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691568308"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691568591","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691568591"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691569221","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691569221"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini hapo kale pua la tembo lilikuwa fupi na nono."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691571904","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691571904"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILIKUWA"," userResponse":" LILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691572369","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691572369"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691573161","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691573161"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIATU"," userResponse":" KIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691574439","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691574439"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOWEKWA"," userResponse":" KILICHOWEKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691575496","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691575496"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" KATIKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691575747","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691575746"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691576192","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691576192"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USO"," userResponse":" USO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691576797","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691576797"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lilikuwa kama kiatu kilichowekwa katikati mwa uso wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691579692","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691579692"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691580199","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691580198"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691580803","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691580803"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691581699","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691581698"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAZAA"," userResponse":" AKAZAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691582529","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691582529"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691583466","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691583466"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691584393","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691584393"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja tembo akazaa mtoto aliyekuwa mdadisi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDADISI"," userResponse":" MDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691588830","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691588830"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691589004","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691589004"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691589438","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691589438"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALI"," userResponse":" SWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691589651","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691589651"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691590125","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691590125"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691590778","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691590778"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNYAMA"," userResponse":" MNYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691592032","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691592032"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alikuwa na swali kwa kila mnyama aliyemuona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEMUONA"," userResponse":" ALIYEMUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691595082","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691595082"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691595265","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691595265"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691595798","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691595798"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691597173","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691597172"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMDADISI"," userResponse":" ALIMDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691597758","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691597758"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo alimdadisi twiga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691599837","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691599837"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691600292","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691600292"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691600796","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691600796"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGO"," userResponse":" SHINGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691601250","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691601250"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKO"," userResponse":" LAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691601514","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691601514"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691602339","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691602339"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini shingo lako ni refu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REFU"," userResponse":" REFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691605020","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691605020"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia alidadisi kuhusu kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691606226","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691606226"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia alidadisi kuhusu kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDADISI"," userResponse":" ALIDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691606897","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691606897"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia alidadisi kuhusu kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUHUSU"," userResponse":" KUHUSU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691607700","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691607700"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia alidadisi kuhusu kifaru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFARU"," userResponse":" KIFARU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691610159","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691610158"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691610405","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691610404"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691610889","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691610889"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691611369","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691611369"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEMBE"," userResponse":" PEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691611980","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691611980"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691612407","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691612407"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691612877","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691612877"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHA"," userResponse":" NCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691614327","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691614327"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOCHONGOKA"," userResponse":" ILIYOCHONGOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691615102","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691615101"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni kwa nini pembe yako ina ncha iliyochongoka sana?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691618039","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691618039"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691618226","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691618226"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691618795","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691618795"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691619277","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691619276"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691620517","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691620517"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMDADISI"," userResponse":" ALIMDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691621287","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691621287"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691621998","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691621998"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691622597","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691622597"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691622969","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691622968"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691623454","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691623454"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691624436","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691624435"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo pia alimdadisi kiboko Kwa nini una macho mekundu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEKUNDU"," userResponse":" MEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691627311","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691627311"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691627803","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691627801"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691628306","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691628305"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUWA"," userResponse":" HUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691629308","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691629308"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAKULA"," userResponse":" UNAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691630178","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691630178"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691633360","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691633360"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMDADISI"," userResponse":" ALIMDADISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691633954","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691633953"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimdadisi mamba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691637227","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691637227"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANANGU"," userResponse":" MWANANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691638622","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691638622"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIULIZE"," userResponse":" USIULIZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691639251","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691639251"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691639950","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691639949"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASWALI"," userResponse":" MASWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691640405","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691640405"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691640936","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691640935"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691641598","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691641598"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691642066","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691642066"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691643166","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691643166"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanangu usiulize wanyama maswali kama hayo mama yake alimwambia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691646128","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691646128"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIONDOKA"," userResponse":" ALIONDOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691646802","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691646802"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIWA"," userResponse":" AKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691647784","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691647784"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KANUNA"," userResponse":" KANUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691648233","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691648233"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691648708","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691648708"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691649512","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691649512"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliondoka akiwa kanuna na kwenda kucheza."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691652706","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691652706"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691653339","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691653339"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691653974","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691653974"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWEREVU"," userResponse":" MWEREVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691654895","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691654895"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691655716","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691655716"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPESI"," userResponse":" UPESI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691656833","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691656833"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIFUATE"," userResponse":" NIFUATE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691657372","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691657372"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWENDE"," userResponse":" TWENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691658120","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691658119"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691660877","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691660877"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULE"," userResponse":" KULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691661631","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691661631"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAONA"," userResponse":" UTAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691662451","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691662451"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBACHO"," userResponse":" AMBACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691663074","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691663074"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691663635","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691663635"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" HULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691664451","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691664451"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kule utaona ambacho mamba hula jioni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691667531","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691667531"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691667711","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691667710"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691668312","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691668312"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691669419","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691669419"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMFUATA"," userResponse":" ALIMFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691670286","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691670286"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691670815","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691670815"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAKA"," userResponse":" MPAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691671564","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691671563"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa Tembo alimfuata Kunguru mpaka mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691675664","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691675664"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIPENYEZA"," userResponse":" ALIJIPENYEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691676163","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691676162"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691677174","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691677174"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIANZI"," userResponse":" MIANZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691677675","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691677675"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691678581","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691678581"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSIMAMA"," userResponse":" KUSIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691679063","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691679063"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691679622","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691679622"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINGO"," userResponse":" KINGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691679832","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691679831"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691680362","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691680362"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipenyeza kwenye mianzi na kusimama kwenye kingo ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691683637","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691683637"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAZAMA"," userResponse":" ALITAZAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691684300","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691684300"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691684440","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691684439"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691684942","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691684942"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691685163","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691685163"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691686050","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691686050"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUULIZA"," userResponse":" KUULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691687224","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691687224"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691688101","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691688101"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691688592","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691688592"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YUKO"," userResponse":" YUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691689685","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691689685"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitazama ndani ya maji na kuuliza Mamba mwenyewe yuko wapi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691693084","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691693084"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HABARI"," userResponse":" HABARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691693821","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691693821"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691694729","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691694728"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILISEMA"," userResponse":" LILISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691695175","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691695175"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691695803","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691695803"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691696042","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691696042"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691696505","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691696505"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Habari jiwe lilisema hapo karibu na mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" MTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691698977","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691698977"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HABARI"," userResponse":" HABARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691699212","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691699212"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691699896","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691699896"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691700773","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691700771"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIBU"," userResponse":" ALIJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691701334","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691701333"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691701575","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691701575"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691702295","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691702294"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691703223","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691703223"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691704224","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691704223"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASEMA"," userResponse":" AKASEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691706824","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691706824"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LABDA"," userResponse":" LABDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691707743","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691707743"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAWEZA"," userResponse":" UNAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691709194","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691709194"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKANIELEZA"," userResponse":" UKANIELEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691710069","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691710069"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691710533","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691710533"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" HULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691711157","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691711157"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691711612","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691711612"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691712555","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691712555"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Labda unaweza ukanieleza mamba hula chakula gani jioni?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691716670","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691716670"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAMA"," userResponse":" INAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691717394","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691717394"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691717996","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691717996"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691719100","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691719100"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITAKWAMBIA"," userResponse":" NITAKWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691719594","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691719594"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691719987","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691719987"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HULA"," userResponse":" HULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691720591","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691720591"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691721155","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691721155"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691722297","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691722296"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILISEMA"," userResponse":" LILISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691722764","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691722764"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691723179","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691723179"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inama kidogo na nitakwambia mamba hula chakula gani lilisema jiwe lile."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" LILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691725656","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691725656"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691725797","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691725795"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691726321","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691726321"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691727453","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691727452"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIINAMA"," userResponse":" ALIINAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691728066","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691728066"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691728974","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691728973"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691729846","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691729846"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691730450","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691730450"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691730894","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691730893"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691731329","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691731329"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LILE"," userResponse":" LILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691732080","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691732080"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliinama chini karibu kabisa na jiwe lile kisha..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691734545","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691734545"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691734792","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691734792"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691735487","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691735487"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691735747","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691735747"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691736299","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691736299"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691737229","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691737228"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691738387","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691738386"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNYWANI"," userResponse":" KUNYWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691738691","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691738691"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWA"," userResponse":" MWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691739277","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691739276"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa mamba ilikuwa kunywani mwa mamba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691742263","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691742263"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691743356","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691743355"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAKULA"," userResponse":" ATAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691743925","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691743924"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691744436","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691744436"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691744946","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691744946"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691745820","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691745820"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691746492","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691746492"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691747199","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691747199"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJANJA"," userResponse":" MJANJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691748895","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691748894"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEMSHAWISHI"," userResponse":" ALIYEMSHAWISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691749437","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691749437"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691749631","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691749631"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691750140","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691750140"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691750626","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691750626"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691751413","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691751413"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba atakula nyama yako leo alisema kunguru mjanja aliyemshawishi mtoto wa tembo kwenda mtoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTONI"," userResponse":" MTONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691754310","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691754309"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691754488","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691754488"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691755222","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691755221"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691756123","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691756123"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAKITA"," userResponse":" AKAKITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691757035","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691757034"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIGUU"," userResponse":" MIGUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691757429","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691757429"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691757961","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691757960"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691758520","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691758520"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUVU"," userResponse":" NGUVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691759148","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691759148"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691760708","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691760708"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKASIMAMA"," userResponse":" AKASIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691761393","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691761393"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691762081","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691762080"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691762874","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691762874"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANZA"," userResponse":" AKAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691764126","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691764125"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIVUTA"," userResponse":" KUJIVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691764634","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691764633"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691765750","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691765750"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo akakita miguu yake yenye nguvu chini akasimama imara na akaanza kujivuta na kujivuta."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIVUTA"," userResponse":" KUJIVUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691767843","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691767842"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691768493","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691768493"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAE"," userResponse":" NAE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691770008","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691770008"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAIKAMATA"," userResponse":" AKAIKAMATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691770682","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691770682"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VEMA"," userResponse":" VEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691771204","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691771203"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691771430","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691771430"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691772131","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691772131"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691772347","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691772347"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691772989","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691772988"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691774944","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691774943"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba nae akaikamata vema pua ya mtoto wa tembo hakuiachia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUIACHIA"," userResponse":" HAKUIACHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691777802","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691777802"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691778045","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691778045"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691778668","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691778667"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691778862","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691778862"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691779539","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691779539"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691781344","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691781343"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAVUTIKA"," userResponse":" IKAVUTIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691782155","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691782155"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691784049","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691784048"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKAREFUKA"," userResponse":" IKAREFUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691785197","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691785196"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691786634","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691786634"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua ya mtoto wa tembo ikavutika ndefu ikarefuka zaidi mpaka...."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAKA"," userResponse":" MPAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691789000","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691789000"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Puu akaanguka na kufika chini kwa mgongo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUU"," userResponse":" PUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691791163","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691791163"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Puu akaanguka na kufika chini kwa mgongo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAANGUKA"," userResponse":" AKAANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691791738","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691791738"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Puu akaanguka na kufika chini kwa mgongo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691792399","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691792399"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Puu akaanguka na kufika chini kwa mgongo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFIKA"," userResponse":" KUFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691793100","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691793100"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Puu akaanguka na kufika chini kwa mgongo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691793358","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691793357"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Puu akaanguka na kufika chini kwa mgongo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691794024","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691794023"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Puu akaanguka na kufika chini kwa mgongo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGO"," userResponse":" MGONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691796991","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691796990"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691797336","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691797335"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691798110","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691798109"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" KUKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691798802","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691798801"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691799591","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691799590"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKE"," userResponse":" CHAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691800591","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691800591"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691801693","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691801693"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZAMA"," userResponse":" ALIZAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691802199","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691802199"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691803386","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691803385"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKOMEA"," userResponse":" KUTOKOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691803867","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691803866"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691804493","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691804493"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya kukosa chakula chake mamba alizama na kutokomea kwenye maji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691807504","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691807503"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliangalia pua yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691807709","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691807709"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliangalia pua yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691808344","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691808344"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliangalia pua yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691809639","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691809639"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliangalia pua yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANGALIA"," userResponse":" ALIANGALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691810063","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691810063"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliangalia pua yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691810617","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691810616"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa tembo aliangalia pua yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691813458","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691813458"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kuona ni wapi iliishia kwa jinsi ilivyokuwa ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691814166","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691814166"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kuona ni wapi iliishia kwa jinsi ilivyokuwa ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONA"," userResponse":" KUONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691814486","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691814486"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kuona ni wapi iliishia kwa jinsi ilivyokuwa ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691815088","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691815088"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kuona ni wapi iliishia kwa jinsi ilivyokuwa ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691816113","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691816113"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kuona ni wapi iliishia kwa jinsi ilivyokuwa ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIISHIA"," userResponse":" ILIISHIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691816743","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691816742"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kuona ni wapi iliishia kwa jinsi ilivyokuwa ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691817390","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691817390"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kuona ni wapi iliishia kwa jinsi ilivyokuwa ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINSI"," userResponse":" JINSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691818346","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691818346"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kuona ni wapi iliishia kwa jinsi ilivyokuwa ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIVYOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIVYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691819033","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691819032"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuweza kuona ni wapi iliishia kwa jinsi ilivyokuwa ndefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEFU"," userResponse":" NDEFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691822755","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691822755"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIREFUKA"," userResponse":" ILIREFUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691823546","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691823546"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691824100","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691824099"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691825249","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691825248"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMUWEZESHA"," userResponse":" KUMUWEZESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691826023","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691826023"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHUMA"," userResponse":" KUCHUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691826765","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691826764"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691827880","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691827880"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALIYOKUWA"," userResponse":" YALIYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691828691","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691828691"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691829589","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691829588"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAWI"," userResponse":" MATAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691829696","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691829696"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691830122","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691830122"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691830687","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691830686"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691831230","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691831230"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilirefuka sana na kumuwezesha kuchuma matunda yaliyokuwa kwenye matawi ya juu ya mti."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691834213","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691834213"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia aliweza kuoga kutumia pua yake wakati wa joto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691835617","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691835617"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia aliweza kuoga kutumia pua yake wakati wa joto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691836531","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691836531"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia aliweza kuoga kutumia pua yake wakati wa joto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGA"," userResponse":" KUOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691837465","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691837465"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia aliweza kuoga kutumia pua yake wakati wa joto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTUMIA"," userResponse":" KUTUMIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691837948","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691837948"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia aliweza kuoga kutumia pua yake wakati wa joto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691838652","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691838652"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia aliweza kuoga kutumia pua yake wakati wa joto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691839745","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691839745"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia aliweza kuoga kutumia pua yake wakati wa joto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691839960","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691839959"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia aliweza kuoga kutumia pua yake wakati wa joto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691840613","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691840613"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pia aliweza kuoga kutumia pua yake wakati wa joto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691843554","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691843553"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAKA"," userResponse":" MPAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691844247","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691844247"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691845114","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691845112"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691845936","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691845936"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691846326","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691846326"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691847041","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691847041"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKONGA"," userResponse":" MIKONGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691847833","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691847832"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIREFU"," userResponse":" MIREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691848521","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691848521"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691849544","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691849544"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YENYE"," userResponse":" YENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691850189","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691850189"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAIDA"," userResponse":" FAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691850802","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691850800"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691852841","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691852841"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1543691852949","data":{"timestamp":" 1543691852949"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20181201_214015"," gameId":" acd019e3-aaf8-41bd-adcc-2c95557e85f7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_15"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mpaka leo tembo wote wana mikonga mirefu na yenye faida kwao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}